saltymilk.com 2009-04-16

# Privacy Policy | SaltyMilk.com

SaltyMilk.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

This privacy policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive.

Salty Milk only collects personal information from a user when the user chooses to give it to us by registering with the site or entering a contest. From time to time Salty Milk will use email addresses to inform registered users of new content, contests, news and other information selected by our editors.  Salty Milk will also use email addresses from time to time to deliver email messages from our partners, advertisers and sponsors. In such event the email will disclose that the recipient is receiving the email from SaltyMilk.com because the recipient is a registered user.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by selecting Unsubscribe at the bottom of a message received.

Salty Milk will not sell or disclose to any third party your name, address, email address or other personal information that specifically identifies you, unless you specifically provide your informed consent, except to the extent necessary to comply with applicable laws or a court order. SaltyMilk.com will allow access to database information to third parties providing technical services, but only to the extent necessary to provide those services.

Salty Milk will use and disclose to third parties information from user registrations and site usage patterns in aggregate form to improve and market the site and to provide traffic information to our partners, advertisers and market researchers. Salty Milk may, at its sole discretion, develop and use consumer research based on an individual user’s use of the web site.

Salty Milk may also use “cookie” technology to improve user’s online experience. We do not extract information about individual users or their computers during this process.

SaltyMilk.com does not maintain any responsibility for information given to one of our advertisers or partner sites. Salty Milk recommends that users read the privacy policy at other web sites before providing any information.

##### Profile

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of your profile.  Registration requires a valid email account for verification purposes.  Your account is protected by a password of your choosing at registration.  If you feel that password has been compromised you may change it at anytime by logging into your account.

##### Third Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

##### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Your use of SaltyMilk.com acknowledges your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
